hey what's up everybody we're back on
the grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski welcome to this episode
this is all about recurring Revenue
building up membership income for
yourself so that you're not in feast or
famine is that you have consistent
months imagine waking up knowing that
this month no matter what happens no
matter what you do you're going to be
able to bring in 10,000 20,000 $40,000 a
month in your business or even aund ,000
a month guaranteed well over the course
of my career that's what we've been able
to do is we've been able to build income
sources that are consistent recurring
Revenue people paying monthly into
subscriptions toble to do this they're
not just buying a one-time thing and I
want to break down for you in this
episode how you can get to this place
why I think that you're a lot closer to
being able to do this than you think and
why you don't need to load it up full of
a bunch of stuff to be able to do this
you don't need to have as much content
as Netflix to be able to do this I
believe that this is the answer for most
people to being able to get out of
fighter flight and be able to experience
what having a successful business is
like Beyond just having to keep showing
up and marketing all the time you know
if you if you got to keep marketing if
you got to keep selling that really is
more like a job and so in what we teach
inside of our program we help a lot of
people many different things High ticket
offers low ticket um uh selling courses
coaching programs membership but I
always bring everything and I hone it
into having a membership program of some
kind one of the things that we like to
include in our membership programs is
having support and accountability for
what people are buying into so they're
not just getting access to information
for information sake information is a
dime a dozen these days you can get a
lot of great information for free I mean
this podcast is a gold mine of
information for for you but the value of
joining my client growth accelerator
program is that you actually get to work
with me personally I'm in that program
helping you through the problems and the
issues in your business guiding you
directing you showing you tweaking your
ads your landing pages your sales offers
all of that and everything and you're
not alone in that process you have our
community but you also have me
personally in there with you and so one
of the things that I recommend is that
if you're a coach or course creator
that's what people are really paying for
they're paying for proximity they're
paying for Access and they're paying to
get closer to you and so you can give
people to pay you monthly just to have
you in their back pocket is what it is
and this is one of the things to realize
is that when you build a membership not
everybody who signs up for the
membership is going to use it all the
time but they like to have it in their
back pocket and that's one of the
thought processes behind having
recurring revenue and a membership that
goes beyond just what a course does
overall people aren't going to just take
action and then they're going to leave
your your your membership instead what
you're doing is you're you're becoming a
part of their lifestyle you're becoming
a part of what they can rely on part of
their success strategy for whatever that
thing is that you help them with okay so
what I want you to do and we got a lot
of different training on finding your
Niche writing your copy creating your
funnels your ads all that but I want you
to take a step back big picture at your
offer
okay what are you offering how do you
help people and really this is the
question what's the transformation that
you bring to people's
lives what is that end
result like what we do we help coaches
make seven figures in their businesses
from zero we help coaches make eight
figures from zero when they work with us
deeper and become a Consulting client of
ours but in our coaching program and our
membership that's what people come to us
for is making that six and seeven and
then seven figure income
by being able
to get the help they need when they need
it staying up to dat as far as what is
the most important information that's up
to date and having that maintenance
access as well as access to brand new
information as well as the community
aspect and when we bring all of this
together that's valuable to people to
pay monthly for now one of the things
with membership sites I will say this is
that yeah you can charge $10,000 for a
course or a program and get that all up
front but with recurring revenue is you
take a little bit of money over time
maybe $1,000 a month $200 a month $75 a
month whatever range you want to go in
$27 a
month and and and listen we got we got
programs that they they range from this
it's whether it be $11,000 a month
$1,600 a month two grand a month breaks
down to
$24,000 a year for the right client the
right access they'll pay that and they
want that and they want to be able to
have that consistency to know that
you're there for them when they need it
and that goes beyond just a one-time
wham bam thank you ma'am check out take
your money from the credit card type of
a thing it's about building trust and
long-term relationship we talk about
this all the time in our coaching coord
and on our podcast is that everything in
business is built on relationship and
connection the more you nurture that
connection with people the longer they
going to want to stay with you and the
longer they're want to stay connected
with you and that you're not just doing
this for a one-time thing with people
but you're actually doing it for the
long haul this is one of the things that
I can say um we've done a great job with
we have clients that we work with that
we have been working with
for
years like decades even nearly nearly
decades for some of them and and like
why would somebody continue working with
us for decades because there's new
layers and there's new things that
they're unpacking and they're growing
progressively and they're growing with
us in that process and that's the
beautiful part about a membership if you
think about Netflix people have been on
Netflix for decades it's the same exact
thing when you're building a membership
site for what you're doing and then that
compounds you got the Compound Effect
where year over year over year you're
adding more people to your membership
and your revenues start to go up and you
actually are making more money while
doing less work overall that's the
beautiful part about having a membership
is it allows you to actually step into
semi-retirement where you don't have to
work and grind and stress and strive
just to get sales you can actually take
a step back take a year off if you want
not or or you know just bare minimum
just do the bare minimum show up on your
calls show up on your trainings do that
and and and then see where that lands
you see where that takes
you now again I know there some some of
yall you're like gosh I I could I would
be nauseated to work that little okay
great awesome you're like me that you
you know you want to maximize your time
and get the most out of it uh but I have
a lot of clients too they're like I want
to I want to figure out okay bare
minimum amount of work most amount of
Revenue
that's what memberships allows you to do
okay so when you're thinking about a
membership you want to think about what
is the amount of money that somebody
will
spend that will allow you to make the
kind of money that you want to make and
then how many people do you need to get
in the door with that so if you're
charging $97 a month if we break this
down on the Whiteboard
here $97 a month and you have a 100
clients that's
$9700 that's coming
in if you have like one of my clients
does over 2500 clients at
$97 a
month you can basically let's just kind
of do round up the math a little bit
here uh you're looking
at
25 100 add two zeros
$250,000 a month off of that and that's
the beauty of a membership and you would
only have to show up maybe two hours a
week for that group and then you know
five six hours a week for your marketing
an hour or two a day that's it that's
what you're able to do and that's what
you're able to accomplish in
this and so like what do you actually
put into a membership like this well you
put the solution that somebody's looking
for you you instead of it just being a
course that they buy one time they get
access
to the course they get access to a
community whether it be a Facebook group
that's how we do it
simple they get access to maybe a a
learning library with other courses if
you have those in there they get access
to ask questions there's live calls that
they can
join and people will pay you monthly to
be able to be a part of a community that
does this and then the beautiful part
about it is is that some of those people
will want to ascend and pay high ticket
with you 20,000
$30,000 of an offer that they can take
to the next level with that okay so
again what you want to do is you want to
look at how do you help people what is
that thing that you help people with and
if you don't understand that that's the
first place you want to start with and
then we learn to build out our our offer
we structure what we're going to
actually sell to people and then we
start marketing it we find the people
that are looking for that thing and we
get in front of as many of those people
as possible whether it be through lead
magnets through advertising campaigns
through social media content to show up
to them to be able to deliver this
value that is coming through this
membership right here okay and so by
creating this recurring Revenue people
will stay on when you start adding new
content consistently every single month
when they can get their questions
answered whenever they want to when
there's guidance and direction that they
can rely on and count
on and that you're going to be there for
them to help them every step of the way
to do that they want to spend time with
you they want to be a part of your tribe
they want to be a part of your community
and this is why in your
business when you can embody what you're
selling you become a product of the
thing that you're selling when you
become a product of your membership when
you become the product that people are
looking to become like when you become a
role model to your clients they will
want to become a part of whatever that
thing is that you're offering and you
got to learn how to persuade people that
it's going to be the thing that they
want you got to learn how to sell this
to people and so this is where tapping
into what drives people to purchase is
the number one skill that you can learn
it goes above and beyond just mindset
but it's learning how to sell to people
it's learning how to get people to say
yes instead of no or maybe or sometime
later when they see the thing that
you're offering and so there's a way of
communicating with people that does this
there's a there the there's a a
structure to the way that you talk the
words that you say how you string them
together that lets people see and
believe that they're going to get the
result with you the only reason why
anybody joins your membership is they
believe that there is an outcome and a
result that they will get by being a
part of your
membership but same with courses same
with coaching program same with
Consulting and so now your job is to
sell them on the fact that they're going
to be able to get that thing that
they're going to be able to experience
that thing that you're selling them on
that their dream outcome is going to be
delivered to them
and so we do this through sales
presentations and our
marketing we find people on social media
we get them to watch some kind of a
video sales presentation video
presentations video content is the
number one way that people engage and
make buying decisions and for every hour
that somebody spends with you on video
they'll be they'll be willing to spend
at least
$1,000 that year with you so if your
membership is $47 a month one hour of
video content or or two 30 minute videos
is enough to get somebody to say okay
great I'm ready to jump in on this if
you're charging $10,000 they might need
to watch 10 hours of content with you
just to really get immersed into your
world that
immersion to see
okay I got this information and you give
your best information away for free so
when we're marketing it we want to
figure out what is the desired outcome
that somebody wants what is the outcome
that we deliver from from our
membership and then what we do is we
give the information piece of it away
for free in the form of YouTube social
media content lead magnets to grow your
email list in emails that we send out
and then by doing that that draws people
to us and they want to become a part of
our ecosystem and our membership and
then what you got to do is you got to
serve those clients you got to have
Milestones that they're looking to to uh
work towards you got to learn how to
lead the group you got to you got to
lead the community and that's a skill
set that you can learn you can be
mentored on by becoming a part of a
community that does this really well
like our client growth accelerator
Community you're able to see how we run
our group how we promote how we get
people to stay engaged and to stay with
us for year after year after
year so again I'd love to have you be a
part of that we help you with your Niche
we help you with your ads with your
message with your sales we optimize
everything with
you so that you have consistent income
so that you have Clarity in your
messaging so that you have massive
impact you can finally have that
financial and time Freedom that you're
looking for and that's what we deliver
in our in our client growth accelerator
program I'd love to have you become a
part of that and be a part of what we're
doing in there with coaches we're we're
creating a brand new thing that's never
before been seen in the coaching
industry before by turning it on its
head and people can see the difference
by being a part of a community that
really is changing the game with
Integrity with truth with honesty with
what's Cutting Edge with what's actually
working and I'm and I'm so grateful
every single day for the clients that we
get to work with and I'd love to have
you be a part of that with us so listen
if this podcast has helped you make sure
to subscribe make sure to check out the
other episodes that we have share it
with somebody and I'd love to work with
you in my coaching program in our
membership in our Mastermind to be able
to help
you break past just trying to make this
online thing work and actually start
making six and seven figures all right
we'll talk soon everybody have a good
one
[Music]
[Applause]